這個星球在運行出我們的宇宙
indicating that when the planet
進入另一個宇宙時
moves out of our universe and into the other,
其時間經常會被加速
its time constant undergoes an acceleration.
你能說簡單點讓傻子也能聽懂嗎
Can you translate that for dumb guys
而且這個傻子可能還有點醉了
who might also be a little drunk?
我們經歷了11天
11 days have passed for us.
但對于這個星球來說  時光大約流逝了
But for the planet, approximately 700 years
-七百年  -等等
- have elapsed. - Wait.
你是說距離我上次來的時候
You're telling me that seven centuries have passed
已經有七個世紀了
since I was here before?
沒錯  指揮官
That is correct, Commander.
好  聯盟總部會很希望得到我們提供的信息
All right, Union Central's gonna want whatever we can give them,
那我們就四處看看  艾薩克
so let's take a look around. Isaac,
對這座城市集中發射密集的掃描光束
focus a tight scanning beam on the city.
我們得知道這些人的穿著
Got to know what these people are wearing,
這樣我們好合成比較適宜的衣物
if we're gonna-synthesize the proper clothing. -